<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CHOCUI</string>

    <!-- Cancer-->
    <string name="Cancer_Label">
        What is Cancer?
    </string>

    <string name="Cancer_Info">
        Cancer is the disease of cells.
        Cells are building blocks of organs and tissue of the body.
        Cancer begins when the cell or cells begin to multiply and grow without control.
        These cancerous cells stop working properly and as their number increases, they form a lump or tumor.
        Should it not be treated in time, the cancerous cells take over the normal cells.
    </string>

    <string name="Cancer_Info2">
        Childhood cancers are different to adults in that they tend to occur in the child\'s organs,
        they look different under a microscope and respond differently to treatment as it is more favorable.
        Cure rates for childhood cancer is much higher than in adults.
    </string>


    <!-- Blood-->
    <string name="Blood_Label">
        Blood Disorders
    </string>

    <string name="Blood_Info">
        The central portion of flat bones and vertebrae is filled with red spongy tissue called bone marrow which is the factory of blood cells.
        When bone marrow fails to produce blood cells, that is called aplastic anaemia or bone marrow failure.
        This lack of cells results in pancytopaenia which is when all three blood cell types are decreased.
    </string>

    <string name="Blood_Info2">
        Anaemia:\n
        • The lack of red blood cells causes weakness, tiredness, breathlessness, and a pale appearance.\n
        • Usually measured as haemoglobin levels.\n\n
        Platelets:\n
        • Low platelets cause easy bruising, nose and gum bleeding, and can cause serious internal bleeding.\n
        • The most serious internal bleed is bleeding in the brain.\n\n
        White Blood Cells:\n
        • Low white blood cells result in the body being unable to fight infections.\n
        • Causes unexplained fevers.
    </string>

    <string name="Blood_Info3">
        Anaemia is a sign/symptom of the lack of red blood cells and has many causes, but it is not a diagnosis.\n
        • Bone marrow infiltration (e.g. leukemia) affects red blood cell production.\n
        • Bone marrow failure may affect all cells (aplastic anaemia) or only red blood cells (red cell aplasia).\n
        • Iron deficiency is the most common cause and found in early stages of childhood under the age of 6.\n
        • Destruction of red blood cells in the blood and spleen (haemolytic anaemia) causes jaundice (yellow eyes) with anaemia.\n
        • Chronic blood loss.
    </string>

    <!-- Types-->


</resources>